[Music]
The name of the company is Reprex, this
is a data science expression. It means
reproducible example: we help to create
the automation of small data tasks that
small organizations don't have a staff for.
So if you can do this once, you can
do it second time, third time, fourth time...
So that is what reprex means and that is what
we do. We work with the data inequalities.
We think that big data creates
inequalities because small NGOs that want to
fight climate change or greenwashing or
those music organizations that want to
give womxn an equal voice in music do
not really have a good access to data.
I've been working with the music
industry for 10 years in 12 countries
and I always saw that if you have a
small music label and you want to make
sure that your data is available for
YouTube or Spotify so that your artists get
paid you have to fill in a lot of data.
You don't have a data team for this we
want to prepare this for you in a way.
Then make it reproducible again and
again and again.
"Doing good and doing business" speaks to
me because I always wanted to do a
company that is not only about profit.
We know a lot about what's going wrong with
the ecosystems of the Earth, but how we
change how people act is more
interesting. So I would like to build a
company that helps in these things.
The Hague is already the Smartest City
it won last year this award.  The Hague is
an ideal location for us because it
is a center of international
organizations and knowledge
organizations like the Europeana, the
Koninklijke bibliotheek, and then of course
the Royal Conservatory and the PAARD.
If you vote for us, you also vote for the Hague,
because we want to bring here large data
collaborations from the world and that
will help the Hague remain the Smartest
City in the world.